{
  "nodes": {
    "start": {
      "question": "What are you having trouble with?",
      "options": {
        "wallet": "Problems with my wallet",
        "exchange": "Problems with an exchange",
        "done_no_help": "Other"
      }
    },
    "exchange": {
      "question": "What exchange?",
      "options": {
        "exchange_poloniex_delist": "Poloniex",
        "exchange_other": "Other"
      }
    },
    "exchange_poloniex_delist": {
      "answer": "Poloniex delisted DigiByte.  There is no way to recover your coins now.  Your only chance and it is a small one is to contact a lawyer",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "exchange_other": {
      "question": "What problem do you have?",
      "options": {
        "format_receive": "Invalid address when I try to withdraw DGB",
        "format_send": "Invalid address when I try to deposit DGB",
        "exchange_cant_help": "Other"
      }
    },
    "exchange_cant_help": {
      "answer": "You will need to contact the exchange for assistance.",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "format_receive": {
      "answer": "The person/company trying to send you funds is using outdated code.  Try providing them a legacy address(one that starts with D).  If your wallet does not have this option download <a href='#' class='popup-info' key='coinomi'>Coinomi</a> and use it.",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "format_send": {
      "answer": "The wallet you are using is outdated.  Recommend installing <a href='#' class='popup-info' key='coinomi'>Coinomi</a> as it supports all modern address formats.",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet": {
      "question": "Is the wallet DigiByte Go?",
      "options": {
        "dead_go": "Yes",
        "wallet_not_go": "No"
      }
    },
    "dead_go": {
      "answer": "DigiByte Go is no functional. You can get your recovery phrase by opening your GO wallet. Then click Settings. Under wallets and integrations select/click the wallet name you want to get a backup phrase for. Click Backup. There is a couple of safety popups you need to click. If you have a spending password you will need to enter it. And there are your backup phrase words. Your wallet(s) can be recovered and we offer two different recovery options.",
      "question": "Which recovery option would you like to try?",
      "options": {
        "recover_digisweep": "Willing to pay 1% for simple recovery",
        "recover_go_coinomi": "Free but has some hoops to jump through"
      }
    },
    "recover_digisweep": {
      "answer": "<h3>To recover your funds</h3><ol><li>Download and install <a href='#' class='popup-info' key='coinomi'>Coinomi</a> on your device</li><li>Go to <a href='https://DigiSweep.digiassetX.com' target='_blank'>DigiSweep.digiassetX.com</a></li><li>Read the first page then hit Start</li><li>Enter your 12 to 24 word mnemonic in to the mnemonic field</li><li>Get a new receive address from Coinomi and put that in the Coin Address field</li><li>If you have any <a href='#' class='popup-info' key='digiassets'>DigiAssets</a> place an address in the Asset Address filed for them to be sent to(can not be the same as coin address)</li><li>Press scan Mnemonic and wait for it to finish</li><li>For most people you will want to select the Send button.  If you are technically inclined and have a core wallet you can chose the Build button</li></ol>",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "recover_go_coinomi": "Want to try the free method to recover DigiByte Go",
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "recover_go_coinomi": {
      "answer": "<p>If you have any <a href='#' class='popup-info' key='digiassets'>DigiAssets</a> select that you want to try the easy method below</p><p>Install the <a href='#' class='popup-info' key='coinomi'>Coinomi</a> app, download link: <a href='https://www.coinomi.com/en/downloads/' target='_blank'>https://www.coinomi.com/en/downloads/</a></p><p>When prompted, enter your 12-word DigiByte Go recovery phrase. You will see a slider for Advanced Settings which gives you BIP39 options, leave this off for now.</p><p>Proceed to the next screen where it will get you to password-protect this on your phone, you may proceed with a password or drag the slider to the left to proceed without password-protection.</p><p>At the list of new coins to add, you can tap once on DigiByte then press the \"+\" to add a standard DigiByte coin to the wallet.  You will now be taken back to the main Coinomi screen for DigiByte.  Don't worry that no funds will be found.</p><p>Click the \"+\" symbol and select Add Coins.</p><p>At the list of new coins to add, you can tap once on DigiByte and a small cog will appear to the right-hand side of that row, tap on the cog.</p><p>At the list of new coins to add, you can tap once on DigiByte and a small cog will appear to the right-hand side of that row, tap on the cog.</p><p>Give it a new name, such as \"DigiByte Go\", and then enter a custom derivation path:</p><p>M/44H/0H/0H</p><p>Tap OK, and then tap the \"+\" down the bottom-right. You will now be taken back to the main Coinomi screen for DigiByte.  This time it will find your funds.</p><p>To avoid having to repeat this in the future, click on DigiByte then Receive to get your first DigiByte address on the proper path.  Click the Copy symbol in the top right of the screen.  Now go back to the main window click DigiByte Go then Send.  Paste your address in to the To field.  Select Max then Continue.</p>",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "recover_digisweep": "Want to try the easy method",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_not_go": {
      "question": "What problem are you having?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_wrong_exchange": "Wrong fiat value shown",
        "wallet_cant_recover": "Can't recover my wallet",
        "wallet_cant_send": "Can't send",
        "wallet_not_synced": "Not all funds showing",
        "wallet_wont_load": "Wallet takes forever to load",
        "wallet_wont_sync": "Wallet wont sync",
        "wallet_core_update": "Upgrading Core Wallet",
        "done_no_help": "Other"
      }
    },
    "wallet_wrong_exchange": {
      "answer": "The price shown is for convenience only and is not important.  Currently API that shows price on DigiByte mobile is down.  If you are not using <a href='#' class='popup-info' key='digiassets'>DigiAssets</a>, we recommend using a safe, standard compliant wallet, such as <a href='#' class='popup-info' key='coinomi'>Coinomi</a>.",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_cant_recover": {
      "question": "What wallet type do you have?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_bip39": "Mobile/Hardware(12 to 24 word recovery)",
        "wallet_core_restore": "Core(wallet.dat file)"
      }
    },
    "wallet_bip39": {
      "question": "What problem are you having?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_bip39_invalid_word": "Says words are invalid",
        "wallet_bip39_standards": "Recovered on a different wallet and balance is 0",
        "done_no_help": "Other"
      }
    },
    "wallet_bip39_invalid_word": {
      "answer": "This is usually a result of typing a word in incorrectly.  Please make sure all the words are spelt exactly the same as found on this <a href='https://github.com/bitcoin/bips/tree/master/bip-0039' target='_blank'>word list</a>.  Accents are important if present.",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_bip39_standards": {
      "question": "What wallet where you using before?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_bip39_standards_digibyte_mobile": "DigiByte Mobile",
        "dead_go": "DigiByte Go",
        "wallet_bip39_standards_compliant": "Other"
      }
    },
    "wallet_bip39_standards_digibyte_mobile": {
      "answer": "Unfortunately DigiByte Mobile is not a standard compliant wallet.  You can only restore funds from DigiByte Mobile on DigiByte mobile or use <a href='https://DigiSweep.digiassetX.com' target='_blank'>DigiSweep</a> to move to your new wallet",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_bip39_standards_compliant": {
      "answer": "Your old wallet was likely standard compliant.  If your new wallet does not see the funds you should try using <a href='#' class='popup-info' key='coinomi'>Coinomi</a> instead.",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_core_restore": {
      "question": "What operating system are you running?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_core_restore_windows": "Windows",
        "wallet_core_restore_mac": "macOS",
        "wallet_core_restore_linux": "Linux"
      }
    },
    "wallet_core_restore_windows": {
      "answer": "Open a file explorer and in the address bar type <span class='code'>%appData%\\DigiByte</span> then copy your wallet.dat file to this folder.(If you named it something else rename it to wallet.dat)",
      "question": "Do you need help installing the newest wallet?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_core_update": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_core_restore_mac": {
      "answer": "Goto <span class='code'>~/Library/Application Support/DigiByte/</span> then copy your wallet.dat file to this folder.(If you named it something else rename it to wallet.dat)<br>If files are hidden, reveal them with the keyboard shortcut <span class='code'>⇧ Shift</span> + <span class='code'>⌘ Command</span> + <span class='code'>.</span>.",
      "question": "Do you need help installing the newest wallet?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_core_update": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_core_restore_linux": {
      "answer": "goto <span class='code'>~/.digibyte/</span> then copy your wallet.dat file to this folder.(If you named it something else rename it to wallet.dat)",
      "question": "Do you need help installing the newest wallet?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_core_update": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_core_update": {
      "answer": "<ol><li>Shutdown your core wallet</li><li>Download and install the newest wallet at <a href='https://github.com/digibyte-core/digibyte/releases' target='_blank'>https://github.com/digibyte-core/digibyte/releases</a></li></ol>",
      "question": "Have you run the wallet since the last fork?(July 2019)",
      "options": {
        "wallet_core_stuck": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_wont_load": {
      "question": "What wallet are you using?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_core_stuck": "Core",
        "done_no_help": "Other"
      }
    },
    "wallet_core_stuck": {
      "answer": "Shut down your core wallet.  Once shut down continue below",
      "question": "What operating system are you using?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_core_delete_blocks_windows": "Windows",
        "wallet_core_delete_blocks_mac": "macOS",
        "wallet_core_delete_blocks_linux": "Linux"
      }
    },
    "wallet_core_delete_blocks_windows": {
      "answer": "Open a file explorer and in the address bar type <span class='code'>%appData%\\DigiByte</span> then delete the blocks and indexes folders if they exist.  Install the newest wallet and start it up if you haven't already.",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_core_delete_blocks_mac": {
      "answer": "Goto <span class='code'>~/Library/Application Support/DigiByte/</span> then delete the blocks and indexes folders if they exist.<br>If files are hidden, reveal them with the keyboard shortcut <span class='code'>⇧ Shift</span> + <span class='code'>⌘ Command</span> + <span class='code'>.</span>.<br>  Install the newest wallet and start it up if you haven't already.",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_core_delete_blocks_linux": {
      "answer": "goto <span class='code'>~/.digibyte/</span> then delete the blocks and indexes folders if they exist.  Install the newest wallet and start it up if you haven't already.",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_not_synced": {
      "question": "Have you tried syncing the wallet?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_wont_sync": "No",
        "wallet_core_less_then_have": "Yes: I was using a really old core wallet",
        "done_no_help": "Yes: Other"
      }
    },
    "wallet_wont_sync": {
      "question": "What wallet are you using?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_wont_sync_mobile": "DigiByte Mobile",
        "wallet_core_update": "Core Older then 7.17.2",
        "wallet_core_stuck": "Core Version 7.17.2",
        "done_no_help": "Other"
      }
    },
    "wallet_wont_sync_mobile": {
      "answer": "This is likely a DNS issue caused by a lot of budget / freely provided home routers. You want to do the following steps:\n\nTurn off your WiFi on your phone\nPower off your device\nPower it back on while connected to JUST mobile-data such as a 3G / 4G data connection\nFire up the DigiByte mobile app and wait for the syncing to begin\nOnce syncing has begun, you can re-join your WiFi\nYou must do these steps in this order so that when your phone powers on, it asks your mobile-carrier for DNS. Often times home routers will keep providing stale DNS entries to devices such as Cellphones on WiFi, meaning even if you reboot your phone while on WiFi you still won't have much luck.\n\nIt should begin to sync within a couple of seconds once you have re-opened the app again.\n\nShould you still have issues even following this troubleshooting steps above, you can also go to Menu -> Settings -> Sync blockchain, and it will perform a full re-sync. This will not affect your funds, but will take approx 20-30 minutes.",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_core_less_then_have": {
      "answer": "Download <a href='#' class='popup-info' key='coinomi'>Coinomi</a> or another wallet on your phone then in the debug console run <span class='code'>walletpassphrase yourpassword 60</span> to unlock your wallet then <span class='code'>dumpwallet filename</span> to save your private keys to a file.  Open the file in a text editor and use either Coinomi's sweep function or <a href='https://DigiSweep.digiassetX.com' target='_blank'>https://DigiSweep.digiassetX.com</a> to sweep your funds to the new wallet.",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_cant_send": {
      "question": "There are a few reasons this may be please pick the one that best applies:",
      "options": {
        "wallet_miner": "I mined to the wallet or received lots of small transactions",
        "format_send": "Says address I am sending to is invalid",
        "wallet_core_update": "Core wallet sends but recipient doesn't get it",
        "wallet_asset_cant_send": "Trying to send a <a href='#' class='popup-info' key='digiassets'>DigiAsset</a>"
      }
    },
    "wallet_miner": {
      "question": "What wallet are you using?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_miner_core": "Core",
        "wallet_miner_other": "Other"
      }
    },
    "wallet_miner_core": {
      "answer": "You likely have to many UTXOs in your wallet.  You can fix this by sending a smaller amount to yourself a few times or if you have been mining you may want to go to the console and type <span class='code'>dumpprivkey miningaddress</span>.  Then use <a href='https://DigiSweep.digiassetX.com' target='_blank'>DigiSweep.digiassetX.com</a> to send the funds from the provided private key back to your wallet.",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_miner_other": {
      "answer": "Your wallet is probably no longer functional because there are to many UTXOs.  <a href='https://DigiSweep.digiassetX.com' target='_blank'>DigiSweep.digiassetX.com</a> can be used to move all your funds to a new address and fix this problem.",
      "question": "Did this fix your problem?",
      "options": {
        "done": "Yes",
        "wallet_cant_send": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_asset_cant_send": {
      "question": "Do you have any DigiByte in the Wallet?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_asset_cant_send2": "Yes",
        "wallet_asset_no_funds": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_asset_no_funds": {
      "answer": "You must have at least 0.001 DGB in your wallet to send <a href='#' class='popup-info' key='digiassets'>DigiAssets</a>",
      "question": "Do you still have a problem?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_asset_cant_send2": {
      "question": "Does the address you are trying to send to start with dgb1?",
      "options": {
        "wallet_asset_ask_legacy": "Yes",
        "done_no_help": "No"
      }
    },
    "wallet_asset_ask_legacy": {
      "answer": "Ask the person you are trying to send to, to get a legacy address.  It will show under qr code on there phone.",
      "question": "Do you still need help?",
      "options": {
        "done_no_help": "Yes",
        "done": "No"
      }
    },
    "done": {
      "answer": "Glad we could help you."
    },
    "done_no_help": {
      "warn": {
        "challenge": "<h1>Warning!</h1>There are scammers everywhere.<br>Never accept support in a private message even if they look like an admin.<br>Remember many eyes keep everyone honest.<hr>To continue type 'I wont give away my keys' in the box below",
        "answer": "I wont give away my keys"
      },
      "answer": "Sorry this could not help you.  <br>  Please go to <a href='https://t.me/DGBSupport' target='_blank'>DGBSupport</a> on telegram and ask your question."
    }
  },
  "info" : {
    "coinomi": "Coinomi is a standard compliant, multi-currency wallet, available for Linux, Mac, Windows, Android & iOS.<br>To learn why we recommend it, visit Coinomi's <a href='https://coinomi.com' target='_blank'>website</a>.",
    "digiassets": "DigiAssets is an asset protocol on-top of the DigiByte blockchain. It should not be confused with DigiByte coins which is something else. <a href='https://DigiByte.org/#digiassets' target='_blank'>See more</a>"
  }
}
